FULL STACK DEVELOPER · JR. DEVOPS ENGINEER

Menteşe, Muğla, Rep. Of Turkey

【 (+90) 551-553-6502 | ■ mrhaliliceylan@gmail.com | 🔏 haliliceylan.github.io

☑ haliliceylan | ₩ haliliceylan | Ⅲ haliliceylan | Ⅲ haliliceylan | № CENG390709073 | ❤ haliliceylan

Summary.

Current Freelance Full Stack Engineer and Jr. Devops Engineer at NetaSolution. 2+ years experience specializing in the backend development, infrastructure automation, and computer hacking/security. Super nerd who loves Linux and OS X and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience_

Cloud Native Computing Platform via Google Summer of Code

Remote

Student Developer May 2021 - Sept 2021

- I contributed to CNCF's open source project "Buildpacks"
- Acceptance Test Development Completed.
- Various Bug fixes have been made
- · During this process, I mainly developed with GoLang.
- I took an active part in the decisions taken by participating in the weekly meetings.

Neta Solutions Mugla, Turkey

FREELANCE REMOTE SR. FULL STACK DEVELOPER & FREELANCE REMOTE JR. DEVOPS ENGINEER

March 2020 - Current

- Restaurant Order Management System is developed with Serverless Application Model in AWS SAM and Terraform in Python.
- Laravel application is developed and deployed on AWS EC2. Also AWS Codepipeline and Gitlab CI/CD are designed for staging and auto deployment.
- Flutter and Laravel applications are developed. In Flutter Project, Provider Design Pattern is used. Laravel REST API is generated for Front and Mobile Clients.
- OCPI(Open Charge Point Interface) **Microservice** Application is developed with using **Python**. **RabbitMQ** is used for microservices communication
- Gitlab CI/CD is designed for NuxtJS project deployment.

Neta Solutions Mugla, Turkey

Freelance Remote Sr. Full Stack Developer

July 2019 - March 2020

- Laravel project is developed and refactored.
- Flutter application is developed.

Neta Solutions Mugla, Turkey

Freelance Remote Jr. Full Stack Developer Apr. 2019 - July 2019

- Laravel and NuxtJS projects is developed.
- Customized E-commerce application is developed with Laravel

DiyezMedia Gaziantep, Turkey

JR. BACKEND DEVELOPER

Oct. 2018 - Nov. 2018

• Queue System is implemented to Laravel E-Commerce Project

.udevo Gaziantep, Turkey

JR. BACKEND DEVELOPER

Oct. 2017, Jan. 2018

• CMS Application is developed with **ASP.net**

Honors & Awards

DOMESTIC

2020	1rd Place, Developer Students Club Turkey DSC-FEST	Turkey
2019	Finalist, Siber Yıldız Capture the Flag	Turkey
2019	3rd Place , Hasan Kalyoncu University Global Game Jam19	Gaziantep, Turkey
2018	Finalist, Hasan Kalyoncu University Gastrobilisim Hackathon	Gaziantep, Turkey
2018	Finalist, Hasan Kalyoncu University Global Game Jam 18	Gaziantep, Turkey
2018	1rd Place , Hasan Kalyoncu University Unity Hackathon	Gaziantep, Turkey
2018	Finalist, ITU CEKIRDEK Big Bang Start-up Challenge	İstanbul, Turkey
2017	Finalist, Hasan Kalyoncu University Smart Life Hackathon	Gaziantep, Turkey

Presentation

DSC MSKU & IEEE CS MSKU Github 101

Turkey

Presenter for < Introduction to Github>

Dec. 2020

- · Introduced the Git basic commands.
- Introduced the how to use Visual Studio Code Git Extension.
- Introduced the how to use Github for developing private project with the team members.
- Introduced Pull Request & Fork mechanism.

Mugla Sitki Kocman University Yesil Kampus

Turkey

PRESENTER FOR < CARBON FOOTPRINT PROJECT>

Sep. 2020

- Introduced to what are the potential applications on the University Campus to reduce carbon emissions.
- Introduced to potential applications of Carbon Footprint Project on University Faculties

Developer Students Club Turkey DSCFEST

Turkey Sep. 2020

PRESENTER FOR < DSC MSKU: CARBON FOOTPRINT PROJECT>

- Introduced Carbon Footprint Project.
 Introducted to what are the psychological effects of mobile applications on humans to reduce carbon emissions.
- Introducted to Tech Stack of Carbon Footprint Projects.
- · Live Demo.

DSC MSKU & IEEE CS MSKU Digital Weeks

Turkey

PRESENTER FOR <FLUTTER ON DARTPAD>

Apr. 2020

- · A visual memory game was developed with the participants..
- Introduced to Dart Functions & Variables.
- Introduced to Flutter Widgets and State Managements.

DSC MSKU & IEEE CS MSKU: Flutter Study Jam

Mugla, Turkey

Dec. 2019

PRESENTER FOR <FLUTTER HELLO WORLD WORKSHOP>

- Introduced Flutter framework for cross applications
- Simple Flutter counter application is developed with the participants
- Introduced to how to integrate Material Design with Flutter.

Program Committees

2020	Lead , Developer Student Club Mugla Sitki Kocman University	Mugla, Turkey
2019	Tech Lead , Developer Student Club Mugla Sitki Kocman University	Mugla, Turkey
2018	Lead, IEEE Hasan Kalyoncu University Computer Society	Gaziantep, Turkey

Education

MSKU(Mugla Sitki Kocman University)

HKU(Hasan Kalyoncu University)

Mugla, Turkey

B.S. IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Sep. 2019 - Current

• Started as a lateral transfer student in 2nd grade

Gaziantep, Turkey

B.S. IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2017 - Sep. 2019